genders = [
    {"Frage":"Band (Musikgruppe)","Antwort":"die Band","answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Band (Streifen)","Antwort":"das Band","answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Band (Buch)","Antwort":"der Band","answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Jahr", "Antwort":"das Jahr", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Beispiel", "Antwort":"das Beispiel", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Zeit", "Antwort":"die Zeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Mensch", "Antwort":"der Mensch", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Deutsch", "Antwort":"das Deutsch", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kind", "Antwort":"das Kind", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Tag", "Antwort":"der Tag", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Land", "Antwort":"das Land", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Frage", "Antwort":"die Frage", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Haus", "Antwort":"das Haus", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Fall", "Antwort":"der Fall", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Arbeit", "Antwort":"die Arbeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Hand", "Antwort":"die Hand", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Stadt", "Antwort":"die Stadt", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Herr", "Antwort":"der Herr", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Problem", "Antwort":"das Problem", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Welt", "Antwort":"die Welt", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Recht", "Antwort":"das Recht", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Ende", "Antwort":"das Ende", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Million", "Antwort":"die Million", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Schule", "Antwort":"die Schule", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Woche", "Antwort":"die Woche", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Seite", "Antwort":"die Seite", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Leben", "Antwort":"das Leben", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Grund", "Antwort":"der Grund", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Auge", "Antwort":"das Auge", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Wort", "Antwort":"das Wort", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Geld", "Antwort":"das Geld", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Sache", "Antwort":"die Sache", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Art", "Antwort":"die Art", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Bereich", "Antwort":"der Bereich (selten: das Bereich)", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Weg", "Antwort":"der Weg", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Stunde", "Antwort":"die Stunde", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Name", "Antwort":"der Name", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Geschichte", "Antwort":"die Geschichte", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gesellschaft", "Antwort":"die Gesellschaft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kopf", "Antwort":"der Kopf", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Paar", "Antwort":"das Paar", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Möglichkeit", "Antwort":"die Möglichkeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Unternehmen", "Antwort":"das Unternehmen", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Bild", "Antwort":"das Bild", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Buch", "Antwort":"das Buch", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Wasser", "Antwort":"das Wasser", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Stelle", "Antwort":"die Stelle", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Form", "Antwort":"die Form", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Mark", "Antwort":"die Mark", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Entwicklung", "Antwort":"die Entwicklung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Monat", "Antwort":"der Monat", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Familie", "Antwort":"die Familie", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Morgen", "Antwort":"der Morgen", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Abend", "Antwort":"der Abend", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Aufgabe", "Antwort":"die Aufgabe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Universität", "Antwort":"die Universität", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Sinn", "Antwort":"der Sinn", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Staat", "Antwort":"der Staat", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Ziel", "Antwort":"das Ziel", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Freund", "Antwort":"der Freund", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Thema", "Antwort":"das Thema", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Person", "Antwort":"die Person", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Euro", "Antwort":"der Euro", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Nacht", "Antwort":"die Nacht", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Ding", "Antwort":"das Ding", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Raum", "Antwort":"der Raum", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Blick", "Antwort":"der Blick", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Platz", "Antwort":"der Platz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zahl", "Antwort":"die Zahl", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"System", "Antwort":"das System", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Uhr", "Antwort":"die Uhr", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Straße", "Antwort":"die Straße", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Minute", "Antwort":"die Minute", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gruppe", "Antwort":"die Gruppe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Wert", "Antwort":"der Wert", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Sprache", "Antwort":"die Sprache", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Anfang", "Antwort":"der Anfang", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Ort", "Antwort":"der Ort", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Moment", "Antwort":"der Moment", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Folge", "Antwort":"die Folge", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Interesse", "Antwort":"das Interesse", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Milliarde", "Antwort":"die Milliarde", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Rolle", "Antwort":"die Rolle", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Tür", "Antwort":"die Tür", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Schüler", "Antwort":"der Schüler", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Bedeutung", "Antwort":"die Bedeutung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Text", "Antwort":"der Text", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Ergebnis", "Antwort":"das Ergebnis", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Krieg", "Antwort":"der Krieg", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Weise", "Antwort":"die Weise", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Regierung", "Antwort":"die Regierung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Stück", "Antwort":"das Stück", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Wohnung", "Antwort":"die Wohnung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gespräch", "Antwort":"das Gespräch", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Meter", "Antwort":"der Meter", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Punkt", "Antwort":"der Punkt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Situation", "Antwort":"die Situation", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Lehrer", "Antwort":"der Lehrer", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Preis", "Antwort":"der Preis", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Abbildung", "Antwort":"die Abbildung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Begriff", "Antwort":"der Begriff", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Funktion", "Antwort":"die Funktion", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Boden", "Antwort":"der Boden", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Jahrhundert", "Antwort":"das Jahrhundert", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Werk", "Antwort":"das Werk", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Stimme", "Antwort":"die Stimme", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Rahmen", "Antwort":"der Rahmen", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Richtung", "Antwort":"die Richtung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Programm", "Antwort":"das Programm", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Angst", "Antwort":"die Angst", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Information", "Antwort":"die Information", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kunst", "Antwort":"die Kunst", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Musik", "Antwort":"die Musik", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Politik", "Antwort":"die Politik", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Beruf", "Antwort":"der Beruf", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Regel", "Antwort":"die Regel", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Schritt", "Antwort":"der Schritt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Absatz", "Antwort":"der Absatz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gott", "Antwort":"der Gott", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Auto", "Antwort":"das Auto", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Beziehung", "Antwort":"die Beziehung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Erfahrung", "Antwort":"die Erfahrung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Tisch", "Antwort":"der Tisch", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zukunft", "Antwort":"die Zukunft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Spiel", "Antwort":"das Spiel", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Gefühl", "Antwort":"das Gefühl", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Licht", "Antwort":"das Licht", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Markt", "Antwort":"der Markt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Bank", "Antwort":"die Bank", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Partei", "Antwort":"die Partei", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Verhältnis", "Antwort":"das Verhältnis", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kirche", "Antwort":"die Kirche", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Film", "Antwort":"der Film", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gedanke", "Antwort":"der Gedanke", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Doktor", "Antwort":"der Doktor", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Entscheidung", "Antwort":"die Entscheidung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Prozess", "Antwort":"der Prozess", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Betrieb", "Antwort":"der Betrieb", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zusammenhang", "Antwort":"der Zusammenhang", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gesetz", "Antwort":"das Gesetz", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Arm", "Antwort":"der Arm", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Firma", "Antwort":"die Firma", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kraft", "Antwort":"die Kraft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Student", "Antwort":"der Student", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zuhause", "Antwort":"das Zuhause", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Chance", "Antwort":"die Chance", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Zeitung", "Antwort":"die Zeitung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Erfolg", "Antwort":"der Erfolg", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Grenze", "Antwort":"die Grenze", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Satz", "Antwort":"der Satz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Angebot", "Antwort":"das Angebot", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Internet", "Antwort":"das Internet", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kultur", "Antwort":"die Kultur", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Lage", "Antwort":"die Lage", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Leistung", "Antwort":"die Leistung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Mitglied", "Antwort":"das Mitglied", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Projekt", "Antwort":"das Projekt", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Zimmer", "Antwort":"das Zimmer", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Chef", "Antwort":"der Chef", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zug", "Antwort":"der Zug", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Arzt", "Antwort":"der Arzt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Fuß", "Antwort":"der Fuß", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Körper", "Antwort":"der Körper", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Klasse", "Antwort":"die Klasse", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Lösung", "Antwort":"die Lösung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Höhe", "Antwort":"die Höhe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Junge", "Antwort":"der Junge", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Fenster", "Antwort":"das Fenster", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Luft", "Antwort":"die Luft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Meinung", "Antwort":"die Meinung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Idee", "Antwort":"die Idee", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Produkt", "Antwort":"das Produkt", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Studium", "Antwort":"das Studium", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Vergleich", "Antwort":"der Vergleich", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Mittel", "Antwort":"das Mittel", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Modell", "Antwort":"das Modell", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Natur", "Antwort":"die Natur", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Bett", "Antwort":"das Bett", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kunde", "Antwort":"der Kunde", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Mitarbeiter", "Antwort":"der Mitarbeiter", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Tod", "Antwort":"der Tod", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Geschäft", "Antwort":"das Geschäft", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Spaß", "Antwort":"der Spaß", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Wirtschaft", "Antwort":"die Wirtschaft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Tier", "Antwort":"das Tier", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Bewegung", "Antwort":"die Bewegung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gast", "Antwort":"der Gast", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Sicherheit", "Antwort":"die Sicherheit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Einsatz", "Antwort":"der Einsatz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gebiet", "Antwort":"das Gebiet", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Dank", "Antwort":"der Dank", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Dorf", "Antwort":"das Dorf", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kollege", "Antwort":"der Kollege", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Angabe", "Antwort":"die Angabe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Verfügung", "Antwort":"die Verfügung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Fach", "Antwort":"das Fach", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Herz", "Antwort":"das Herz", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kontakt", "Antwort":"der Kontakt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Menge", "Antwort":"die Menge", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Sommer", "Antwort":"der Sommer", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Unterschied", "Antwort":"der Unterschied", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Anspruch", "Antwort":"der Anspruch", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Antwort", "Antwort":"die Antwort", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Verbindung", "Antwort":"die Verbindung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Vorstellung", "Antwort":"die Vorstellung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Anwendung", "Antwort":"die Anwendung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Alter", "Antwort":"das Alter", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Patient", "Antwort":"der Patient", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Polizei", "Antwort":"die Polizei", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Theater", "Antwort":"das Theater", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Ausbildung", "Antwort":"die Ausbildung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gefahr", "Antwort":"die Gefahr", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gerät", "Antwort":"das Gerät", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Kilometer", "Antwort":"der Kilometer", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Hilfe", "Antwort":"die Hilfe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Computer", "Antwort":"der Computer", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Dollar", "Antwort":"der Dollar", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Verfahren", "Antwort":"das Verfahren", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Vertrag", "Antwort":"der Vertrag", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Maßnahme", "Antwort":"die Maßnahme", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Mitte", "Antwort":"die Mitte", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Ordnung", "Antwort":"die Ordnung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Stoff", "Antwort":"der Stoff", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Beginn", "Antwort":"der Beginn", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Glück", "Antwort":"das Glück", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Wochenende", "Antwort":"das Wochenende", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Professor", "Antwort":"der Professor", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Reihe", "Antwort":"die Reihe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Westen", "Antwort":"der Westen", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Bevölkerung", "Antwort":"die Bevölkerung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Institut", "Antwort":"das Institut", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Osten", "Antwort":"der Osten", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Erde", "Antwort":"die Erde", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Ebene", "Antwort":"die Ebene", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Reise", "Antwort":"die Reise", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Einheit", "Antwort":"die Einheit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Haar", "Antwort":"das Haar", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Nähe", "Antwort":"die Nähe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Prinzip", "Antwort":"das Prinzip", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Vorteil", "Antwort":"der Vorteil", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Struktur", "Antwort":"die Struktur", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Autor", "Antwort":"der Autor", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Bedingung", "Antwort":"die Bedingung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Risiko", "Antwort":"das Risiko", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Wahl", "Antwort":"die Wahl", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Wirkung", "Antwort":"die Wirkung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Brief", "Antwort":"der Brief", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Größe", "Antwort":"die Größe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Macht", "Antwort":"die Macht", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Untersuchung", "Antwort":"die Untersuchung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Veränderung", "Antwort":"die Veränderung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Einfluss", "Antwort":"der Einfluss", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Methode", "Antwort":"die Methode", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Organisation", "Antwort":"die Organisation", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Liebe", "Antwort":"die Liebe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Rede", "Antwort":"die Rede", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Sport", "Antwort":"der Sport", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Augenblick", "Antwort":"der Augenblick", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Diskussion", "Antwort":"die Diskussion", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Forderung", "Antwort":"die Forderung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kreis", "Antwort":"der Kreis", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Technik", "Antwort":"die Technik", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Versuch", "Antwort":"der Versuch", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Krankheit", "Antwort":"die Krankheit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Schwierigkeit", "Antwort":"die Schwierigkeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Tätigkeit", "Antwort":"die Tätigkeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Voraussetzung", "Antwort":"die Voraussetzung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kampf", "Antwort":"der Kampf", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Region", "Antwort":"die Region", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Eindruck", "Antwort":"der Eindruck", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Reaktion", "Antwort":"die Reaktion", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Beitrag", "Antwort":"der Beitrag", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Konzept", "Antwort":"das Konzept", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Linie", "Antwort":"die Linie", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Mund", "Antwort":"der Mund", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Wunsch", "Antwort":"der Wunsch", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Artikel", "Antwort":"der Artikel", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gegensatz", "Antwort":"der Gegensatz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Kapitel", "Antwort":"das Kapitel", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Literatur", "Antwort":"die Literatur", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Rücken", "Antwort":"der Rücken", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zelle", "Antwort":"die Zelle", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Aussage", "Antwort":"die Aussage", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Bürger", "Antwort":"der Bürger", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Himmel", "Antwort":"der Himmel", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Inhalt", "Antwort":"der Inhalt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Wand", "Antwort":"die Wand", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Bibliothek", "Antwort":"die Bibliothek", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Farbe", "Antwort":"die Farbe", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Maß", "Antwort":"das Maß", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Ansatz", "Antwort":"der Ansatz", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Aspekt", "Antwort":"der Aspekt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Bein", "Antwort":"das Bein", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Erinnerung", "Antwort":"die Erinnerung", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kenntnis", "Antwort":"die Kenntnis", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Kurs", "Antwort":"der Kurs", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Papier", "Antwort":"das Papier", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Sekunde", "Antwort":"die Sekunde", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Sonne", "Antwort":"die Sonne", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Umstand", "Antwort":"der Umstand", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Wissenschaft", "Antwort":"die Wissenschaft", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Garten", "Antwort":"der Garten", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Küche", "Antwort":"die Küche", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Wirklichkeit", "Antwort":"die Wirklichkeit", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Druck", "Antwort":"der Druck", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Essen", "Antwort":"das Essen", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Grundlage", "Antwort":"die Grundlage", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Zustand", "Antwort":"der Zustand", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Hälfte", "Antwort":"die Hälfte", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Meer", "Antwort":"das Meer", "answer_class":"neut"},
    {"Frage":"Dienst", "Antwort":"der Dienst", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Gegenstand", "Antwort":"der Gegenstand", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Plan", "Antwort":"der Plan", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Zeitpunkt", "Antwort":"der Zeitpunkt", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Auftrag", "Antwort":"der Auftrag", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Baum", "Antwort":"der Baum", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Freude", "Antwort":"die Freude", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Gemeinde", "Antwort":"die Gemeinde", "answer_class":"fem"},
    {"Frage":"Hinweis", "Antwort":"der Hinweis", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"September", "Antwort":"der September", "answer_class":"masc"},
    {"Frage":"Oktober", "Antwort":"der Oktober", "answer_class":"masc"},
]